hindutav.com 2015-10-30

# Privacy Policy | Hindutav

This is the Privacy Policy for [Hindutav Blog](http://www.hindutav.com/ "Hindutav")

First of all we at Hindutav team want to clear that your privacy is extremely important for us.

In this Privacy Policy we outline the type of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

**Note:** This Privacy policy is subject to revision without further notice.

Your use of this site (www.hindutav.com) is a subject to acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

Below we have mentioned how we make use of **Log Files** and **Cookies**

### 1\. Log Files

Just like other websites out there, we also make use of log files which include the following information:

  * IP (Internet Protocol) addresses
  * Type of Browser
  * Internet Service Provider
  * Referring and exit Pages
  * Number of Clicks

The above information is no way related to your personal information. Actually, it helps us to determine our audience. Where do they come from and what topics interest them. So, that we can optimize our content and website according to them.

### 2\. Cookies

The use of Cookies is quite similar to that of log files. We use them to determine what pages our visitors visit and what interests them the most so that we can optimize our website for them.

If you wish to disable Cookies then you can do so in your browser itself. To get a tutorial on how to disable cookies, visit your web-browser’s official website.

### 3\. Subscription

We use a subscription form on our blog for our visitors, so that they can subscribe to our E-mail updates and Newsletter. The use of our site has to provide their Name and E-mail address in order to subscribe to our website. The Opt-in process is very sophisticated and thus is safe i.e. your information remains in our hands only when your subscribe to our website.

### **4\. Advertising/Monetization of this website**

We don’t have any intention of Monetizing this website anytime in the near future and the content of this website available to anyone above the legal age of 13 to consume.

**We don’t share your E-mail address with anyone.**

* * *

### Further Quarries

Just in case you have any kind of doubt or you want to ask any kind of question.

You can simply use our [Contact-Us Page](http://www.hindutav.com/contact "Contact Us")
